Hey, fall down, fall down, fall down.  Oh [ __ ].
Hey Krishna, you just keep watching
because I will break this pot.
It fell down.
Hey Krishna, Bunty has fallen.  Now you go and break the
pot.
Oh my God, I am scared even to climb up.
Then how will I break this pot?
Hey, go away Krishna.  What are you thinking?
Yes, okay.
Hey, no one should support that Krishna.  And
yes, here's to your party.  Okay
brother, I will not give it.
Hey, come on brother.  Move away, we don't want to come.  [Music]
Kanha, now jump and hold the rope and break the
mutton.
[Music]
Hey, go ahead and drop this Krishna.
Hey, leave the soil, leave it quickly, leave the soil, leave it
quickly, leave the
rope,
leave the rope,
oh God, now I will have to do something.
Leave the girl, leave her
[screaming voice]
Krishna, now break the pot.
Yes yes [music]
friend Muskaan this pot has broken only because of you.
Yes Krishna, take this and eat sweets in this happiness.
[music]